module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'In what area of the human body is a metacarpal bone located?', 
    a: 'Chest',
    b: 'Hand',
    c: 'Foot',
    d: 'Leg',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT considered an Ivy League school?', 
    a: 'Brown University',
    b: 'Dartmouth College',
    c: 'Duke University',
    d: 'Cornell University',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which breed of dog is also known as "Blue Heelers"?', 
    a: 'Australian Cattle Dog',
    b: 'Australian Terrier',
    c: 'Australian Shepherd',
    d: 'Australian Silky Terrier',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the Lucky Charms cereal mascot?',
    a: 'Lucky',
    b: 'Sam',
    c: 'Sunny',
    d: 'Finn',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Cherilyn Sarkisian is the birth name of which famous woman?', 
    a: 'Cheryl Tiegs',
    b: 'Cheryl Hines',
    c: 'Cher',
    d: 'Cheryl Burke',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: '"Please, sir, I want some more." is a famous line from what novel?', 
    a: 'To Kill a Mockingbird',
    b: 'Oliver Twist',
    c: 'The Adventures of Tom Sawyer',
    d: 'Brave New World',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which U.S. President is NOT featured on Mount Rushmore?', 
    a: 'George Washington',
    b: 'Thomas Jefferson',
    c: 'Franklin Roosevelt',
    d: 'Abraham Lincoln',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of Roger Rabbit\'s wife?', 
    a: 'Victoria',
    b: 'Jessica',
    c: 'Vanessa',
    d: 'Jennifer',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'A "Hadouken" is a special attack in what video game?', 
    a: 'Super Smash Bros.',
    b: 'Mortal Kombat',
    c: 'Mike Tyson\'s Punch-Out!!',
    d: 'Street Fighter',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which rock singer bit the head off a bat on stage?', 
    a: 'Ozzy Osbourne',
    b: 'Marilyn Manson',
    c: 'Alice Cooper',
    d: 'Rob Zombie',
    answer: 'a'
  },
];
